"As payment for the potion
that would grow the princess legs,
the witch demanded the princess's
voice, which was peerless in beauty.
So the mermaid princess had her
little tongue cut out by the witch,
and could use her voice no more."
Who's there?!
What are you?!
But man, Dante...
Every time I drop by, you're
further and further in debt.
What do you expect?
Everyone leaves me bills
instead of a damn paycheck!
Hey Dante, are you here?
Sleeping again...
You gotta be kidding me...
What kind of adult spends all of
their time sleeping or eating pizza?
What happened to the jukebox?
Just find a way to fix it.
Don't be ridiculous.
Anyway, you're just too violent!
You don't know how to handle things.
Not machines, and not women either.
--Agreed.
--Lay off.
The only ways this thing's going to
get fixed is by getting parts for it.
Or you could find some way to
get a different one altogether.
But I bet that would be pricey...
This thing's vintage, right?
There's a lot of freaks into
vintage stuff out there, you know.
Hey Dante, why is this the
only record you have framed?
I've played that record more than
any other, but it got scratched...
I framed it 'cause I couldn't
bring myself to just throw it away.
If you like it so much,
why not buy another one?
Look at it and you'll see why.
I don't know the name of
the singer or the song.
Back in the day, that was one
of the records in that jukebox.
It's no use...
It'd be quicker to just go
out and buy a new one, Dante.
Yeah, like I got the money to do that....
Of course you don't. All right then...
It doesn't have anything to do with devils,
so I was planning on handing
it off to someone else, but...
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a job, of course.
There's this abandoned building up north.
And a secret room was discovered in it.
Luckily, the room was airtight, so
its contents were in good condition.
A ton of never-played records
were miraculously preserved there.
The treasure hunters who got wind of this came
to me because they're looking for a bodyguard.
Mr. Dante, thank you very
much for accepting this position.
We feel much more at ease knowing we have
a man of your talent serving as our bodyguard.
Our profession is treasure hunting...
We are lousy when it comes to fighting.
This counts as treasure hunting?
It certainly does.
Didn't you accept this job because you
also thought the goods were worth it?
There are a lot of people out there willing
to pay enormous sums of money for antiques.
Sometimes people will even
kill the owners to get them.
Apparently some people
must really dig their antiques...
Tim, we should liven things up...
why don't you play something?
Yeah, you bet.
What's that?
Huh?
Ah, this?
Now this is something special...
It's by the legendary
rock queen, Elena Huston.
This is the real thing.
This record is filled with her soul,
the purest thing there ever was.
I don't suppose I could request that one?
Sure, why not.
It's not a bad idea to
play it every now and then...
I can hear it...
That's... my...
Not bad... It strikes you right to the core.
Doesn't it? Her voice is
kind of husky, but really good.
She started writing the tunes and lyrics
for these while she was a street musician.
You seem to know your stuff.
Yeah, well...
Well, time for me to get to work.
No you don't... let it play.
You gotta have music if you want to party.
Tim!
Elena...
So she ran away.
Thanks.
There's no doubt about it. That was Elena...
Elena and I were childhood friends.
I was just a plain, good-for-nothing
kid, but Elena was different.
She was this brilliant singer.
How can I say it...
Her voice had this strange
power that drew people in.
And I was one of the spellbound...
I had this intense desire to have
more people listen to her songs.
As many people as I possibly could.
In the beginning all she had was a guitar...
But before long, she got a band together
and put on shows out in the streets.
And soon the whole city knew her voice.
Me, I was playing dress-up
in unfamiliar suits and ties,
going around making the sales pitches.
But with no backing from anyone,
just putting out one record
was further away than a dream...
Ms. Elena Huston, I'm looking
forward to seeing you on stage today...
How long am I going to
have to keep doing this crap?!
We just have to be patient.
Right now what we need to do is grind away
at building a bigger fanbase, however we can.
Grind away, grind away...
You're always like this!
Business! Sales! Fame!
I've had it with this!
Take it easy... The next show's
going to be at a bigger venue.
The next show?! How many
damn shows has it been now?!
I'm sick of this!
The only thing I want is for more and more
people to lose themselves in my music.
That's the only thing I care about...
Why can't you understand that?
Elena...
Then... all of our work
finally paid off or something.
We got our shot at a major debut
and she gradually got more gigs.
When that long-wished-for first album
was released, she started getting popular.
But... some strange things started to
happen to the fans who listened to her.
Strange things?
The fans lost themselves in excitement,
and in the end, all kinds of
people started committing suicide
or even murdering one another
for tickets to her concerts.
Elena! Elena!
And then Elena, herself, began to change...
The more that Elena's
spellbound fans went crazy,
the further she withdrew from me.
Then...
--Elena...
--Sing...
I...
What's going on?!
Is there something you're not satisfied with?
Who are you?! What's happened to everyone?!
Isn't it just what you wanted?
You wanted to have a spellbinding voice
that your fans could not do without.
A devilishly beautiful voice...
that's what you wanted, isn't it?
And you got it, that's all.
Th-That's not--
You want something, you
have to give something.
It's called a tradeoff.
You are me, and I am you.
We're of the same mind and body.
So you'll use this on her?
Yeah... I think she's searching
for this record. Her own songs.
What is Dante the "Devil
Hunter" going to do with her?
The Elena Huston you knew is gone. You saw.
That was nothing but a devil.
I... suppose you're right.
This music's a little
rowdy for a requiem, though.
My voice...
My song...
You want your songs back, don't you?
If you do, you're going to have
to kill those who stand in the way.
You have to kill for your
precious, precious songs.
Th-That's...
Come on, let's kill them...
Let's crush them...
Your songs, the things
most precious to you...
Let's kill, kill, kill... and
then let's kill some more.
You said it, didn't you? That for
your songs you'd sacrifice anything...
For... my songs...
Yes... For my songs. Let's kill!
Ah, wonderful! So wonderful! The best...
The rock queen... Elena Huston!
Elena, stop. Please stop.
Your voice... your songs...
I know this isn't what they were for...
I'm begging you, Elena...
Enough already... Enough...
Elena!
You'll... regret this...
Elena! Elena!
Please, open your eyes, Elena!
Elena!
Hang in there, I'm going to call a doctor.
Record....
What, Elena?
Oh... It was you, wasn't it?
You still... had my... record...
Tim?
Of course! Because it's...
Because you're truly the greatest.
I wish we could be... together again...
Elena...
A tribute to the spirit of the Queen...
What would you ask for if you
could have your wishes granted?
Would you ask to be rich?
Or to have the woman
you're in love with be yours?
You can wish for whatever
you want, it's your business,
but to have one's wishes come
true always comes with its price.
Every deal has a catch.
You'd better be nice and careful.